-请用  -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thanks.
-来了  -来了
- Hey, man. - Hey.
这是什么
What's this?
我在高层有人
I got a source in the ivory tower.
这是她给我的
She gave me that.
认得他吗
Recognize him?
认得
Yeah.
这家伙撬了我的车  是个瘾君子
It's the junkie I caught breaking into my car...
就是我和艾琳运宾汉姆尸体的那晚
the night me and Erin moved Bingham's body.
他叫鲁本·吉尔布莱特
Well, his name is Ruben Gilbright.
我猜是伍兹要利用他
My guess is Woods is gonna use him
杜撰一个谋杀案来嫁祸你
to try and build a homicide case against you.
你真觉得这些家伙谋划得那么远吗
You really think these guys are that far along?
我不确定  但我不想冒险
I'm not sure, but I'd rather not take any chances.
我去调查一下这个鲁本
Right, I'm gonna look into this Ruben,
看看他做什么的  也许可以抓到什么把柄
see what he's about, maybe catch him dirty.
毁掉他最后一点信誉度
Destroy what little credibility he has left.
最好能把这事彻底解决
Hopefully, we'll put this thing to bed, once and for all.
让我来处理
Let me handle it.
你别沾手
You can't get anywhere near it.
我来  老埃
I got this, Al.
交给我
I got it.
到处闲逛是犯法的
You know, it's against the law to loiter.
才不是
No, actually, it's not.
我一整天站在这里都行
I can stand right here all day if I want to.
放轻松
Relax.
我只是开个玩笑  说笑的
It was a joke-- meaningless pleasantry.
我更希望你准时一点
Yeah, I'd prefer you be on time
而不是过来开这种无聊的玩笑
rather than crack meaningless pleasantries.
明白吗
You know what I mean?
明白  我堵车了
Yeah, well, I got jammed up.
但如果这是个问题
But if it's a problem,
我们可以好好解决一下
we can figure it out.
有问题吗
You got a problem?
-什么  -我不喜欢你说话的语气
- Excuse me? - I don't like your tone,
你还欠我两千
or the fact that you owe me two grand.
两千  你在说什么
Two grand? What the hell you talking about?
我要我的钱
I want my money.
你的钱
Your money?
雷
Whoa, Ray.
冷静  冷静
Just chill, chill, chill.
别让我冷静
Don't tell me to chill!
我要拿到我的钱
I want my paper in my hand.
好吧好吧  我会给你的
All right, all right, I'll get you your paper.
就今天
Today.
好  我今天会给你的
Okay, I'll get it to you today.
雷
Ray.
怎么回事
What the hell, man?
-怎么回事  -没事
- The hell was that? Huh? - Never mind.
-有问题啊  -不清楚
- That wasn't cool, bro. - Really not sure.
好
All right.
雷怎么回事
The hell is wrong with Ray, man?
那不是说好的吧
That was uncalled-for, right?
我会解决
I'll handle it. I'll handle it.
雷
Ray?
刚刚到底怎么回事
What the hell was that?
听着鲁赛克  我很抱歉  有个人...
Look, Ruzek, I'm sorry. Was a banger--
他在巷子那边  正在看
he was down the alley. He was watching.
他在说你是个警察  我不得不那么做
He was making you to be a cop. I had to do my thing.
所以你就拿枪指着我的头吗
So you put a gun to my head?
你拿枪指着我
You just put a gun to my head!
听着  好吗
Look, all right?
那家伙是拉丁帮的头头
Dude is a shot-caller for the Latin Hoods.
我费了好大劲
I've been working too hard for too long
才要混进去  我不能就这么毁了
to get in with these guys. I couldn't jeopardize that.
雷  我就在附近  立马就能拿下你
Ray, I'm 15 feet closer, I put your ass down.
你知道的吧
You understand that, don't you?
我知道我在做什么  我是个警察
I know what I'm doing. I'm a cop.
曾经是个警察
Used to be a cop.
你在保护你的伪装身份  我们明白
You were protecting your cover. We get it.
这事就过去了好吗
All right, let's all move on. Yeah?
-好  -很好
- All right. - Great.
雷  雷
Ray. Ray.
藏匿点的消息
The rips on the stash houses--
尸体越来越多了  你有什么消息
bodies are piling up. What are you hearing?
什么都没有
Crickets. I hear nothing.
能帮我们挖掘一下吗
Okay, can you some digging for us?
可以  但有人摇摆了
Yeah, but people are shook.
他们害怕
They scared.
要让他们开口说话
They're gonna need a little bit more spinach
可能要放点好处
if you want them to get talking.
你知道怎么操作
Well, you know the drill.
我们得到的信息越多  你们的好处也越多
You get more spinach when we get more information.
你准备好了吗
You ready to go?
亚当
Hey, look, Adam...
你知道我很擅长的
Come on, you know I'm good for it.
我总能得到好消息
I always deliver gold.
雷  这是最后一次预付
Ray, this is the last advance.
听到了吗
You hear me?
别再拿枪指着我
Don't ever pull a gun on me again.
我也感到遗憾
I feel sorry for the man too,
但雷的事是他的错  不是你的错
but what happened to Ray is his fault, not yours.
别有负罪感
Let that guilt go.
全城小组注意
Units on the city wide,
我们接到多个枪击案报警电话
we're getting multiple reports of shots fired
在南维克瑞斯街1360号
at 1360 South Waycrest.
不远  走吧
Ah, that ain't far. Come on.
5021D
5021 David.
这些报警电话似乎是真的
This call appears to be bona fide.
别挡路  让开
Out of the way! Out of the way!
让大家都过来
Keep these cars coming.
我们要进去了  准备好了吗
We're moving in. You ready?
-有尸体  -收到
- I have a body. - Copy.
凯文  门
Kev, door, door. Door, door, door.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
安全
Clear.
翻译     小酸奶   西之   不高兴童鞋   小萝莉
看到一把枪
I see a gun.
好  安全
All right, we're clear.
翻译     Lynn_宁   H小欠
好
Okay.
两个人倒下  都没有反应
We got two down, both nonresponsive.
校对     小酸奶
小凯
Kev.
凶手在楼内
Active shooter in the building.
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
真见鬼
This sucks.
后期     8T
救命
Help!
-小凯  -芝加哥警署
- Kev? - Chicago PD!
救命
Oh, please!
总监     圈圈
-求你了  帮帮他  -安全
- Please, you gotta help him! - Clear!
拜托
Please!
好的  好的
All right. All right.
好  他的脉搏很弱
All right, he's got a light pulse.
-睁开眼睛  孩子  -过来
- Open your eyes, papi! - Come here.
醒醒  孩子
Come on, kid.
-看着我  -5021  紧急情况
- Look at me, huh? - 5021, emergency.
拜托  拜托  拜托
Come on, come on, come on.
发现第三名被害人
We got a third victim down.
什么情况  兄弟
Talk to me, bro.
不
No!
-不  -头部中枪
- No! - Gunshot wounds to the head.
被害人是孩童   赶紧联系芝加哥消防局
Tender age victim. Roll CFD down here right now.
给我快点
Hurry the hell up.
不  宝贝
No, my baby!
救护车马上来
Ambo on the way.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十九集
刚好发生在我们到达之前
Happened right before we got here.
我们赶到的时候
By the time we arrived,
枪手已经跑了
shooters were already in the wind.
这是另一个藏匿处
It's another stash house rip.
没错  他们也跑了  警长
Yeah, and they got the hell up out of here, too, Sarge.
路上丢了几包海洛因
Dropped a couple bricks of heroin on the way out.
没看到钱
No cash.
海洛因砖上有眼镜蛇的标志
Bricks have a cobra logo this time.
两名守卫都死了  就像其他藏匿点一样
Both guards were dead, just like the other rips.
警长
Sarge.
将弹壳交给弹道分析部门
Okay, get the casings to ballistics.
看看有没有和其他劫案相符的
See if they're a match with the other robberies.
-收到  -最好也收集一下走廊那边大门的痕迹
- Copy. - Door down the hall may as well have been paper.
子弹穿过了那扇门
Bullets went flying through it.
那里的小男孩是无辜遭到牵连的
Little boy in there was collateral damage.
-怎么样了  伙计们  -肯尼
- What's going on, guys? - Kenny.
你怎么来了
Hey, what brings you out here?
我要执行一张搜查令
About to execute a search warrant.
看来我们是迟到了
Looks like we're late to the party.
你们怎么来了
Why you guys here?
我们在追查一伙劫贩
Ah, we've been chasing a rip crew.
他们最近不停地袭击藏匿点
They're hitting stash houses,
偷毒品  主要是海洛因
stealing drugs-- so far, mostly heroin.
这些帮派在黑吃黑
These gangs are eating their own.
-没错  -他来了
- Yeah. - There he is.
我很乐意把我们的情报给你们
Happy to turn over what we got.
很高兴见到你  肯尼
Good to see you, Kenny.
你要把这交给情报部了
You letting Intelligence take this?
瑞秋  放松
Rachael, relax.
如果你们一直在查这个案子
If you guys have been working this,
为什么和高效毒品走私地区数据库冲突
why didn't you de-conflict it with HIDTA?
伙计们  这是罗哈斯警探
Guys, this is Detective Rojas.
我整理过文件  没有明确冲突
I did the paperwork. There were no direct conflicts.
我们接到报警电话
We got an in-service call.
说听到枪声  我们就来了
Said shots fired. Here we are.
这案子是情报部的
Intelligence is taking the lead.
罗哈斯是个好警探
Look, Rojas is good police, right?
她只是会有点冲动
She's just a little rough around the edges.
这不算什么  肯尼
Hey, there's nothing wrong with that, Kenny.
我们会随时告诉你情况
All right, we'll keep you in the loop.
-很高兴见到你  -谢谢  汉克
- Good to see you, man. - Thanks, Hank.
小姐
Ms. Montero.
我是伯吉斯警官  这是厄普顿警察
I'm Officer Burgess. This is Detective Upton.
我们很遗憾
We're so sorry about your loss.
如果可以的话  我们想问你几个问题
If it's okay, we'd like to ask you a few questions.
-我没事  -好的
- I'm okay. - All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
你看到发生了什么吗
Did you see what happened?
没有
No.
我本来在洗澡
I was in the shower.
然后听到走廊传来巨响
Then I heard loud bangs from the hallway.
你知道谁住在
Do you know who's living in the apartment
枪案发生的那间公寓吗
where the shooting happened?
我们才刚搬进来
We just moved in.
这里本来应该是个不错的地方
It was supposed to be a better neighborhood.
你看到什么可疑的人了吗
Okay, did you see anyone suspicious?
有没有人逃走  有没有...
Someone running away, someone...
他们经常和我说  不管发生什么
They always tell you, whatever happens,
都不要和警察说话
you never talk to the police,
但我不在乎了
but I don't care.
这些禽兽夺走了我的孩子
These animals took my boy.
你看到了什么  莎拉
What did you see, Sarah?
有两个人从消防通道跑了
Two men going down the fire escape.
你能形容一下吗
Can you describe them?
拉丁裔
Latinos.
很年轻  二十多岁吧
Young, like, 20.
好的  还有别的吗
Okay. Anything else?
-他们戴着滑雪面罩  -滑雪面罩
- They had ski caps. - Ski caps...
然后他们开着一辆深色的车走了
And they drove off in a dark car.
我听到枪声后
After I heard all the shooting,
我...我就去看菲利克斯
I--I went to look for Felix.
他感觉不舒服  当时正在睡觉
He wasn't feeling well. He was taking a nap.
然后看到他躺在那里
And there he was,
到处都是血
blood everywhere.
天啊
Oh, my God.
不
Ai, no!
No...
不  我的孩子
No, my boy!
不
Ai, no!
我们会陪着你的  好吗
We're gonna stay with you, okay?
跟我们来
Come with us.
我的孩子  我的宝贝
Oh, my boy. Oh, my baby.
我的宝贝
My baby.
今天的劫案和之前两起
Today's rip followed the same MO
作案手法一样
as our previous two.
他们炸门  杀里面的人
They blast the doors open, kill everybody inside,
拿走钱和货  然后就走
grab money and product, and get the hell out of there.
刚比对了两名死者的指纹
Just ran the prints of the two dead guys.
这两名  一无所获
These two. Nothing.
没有名字  没有犯罪记录
No names, no criminal history.
那就一共有六名死去的黑帮成员
That makes six dead bangers.
还有菲利克斯·蒙特罗
And Felix Montero.
刚满十岁
Just turned ten.
我们找菲利克斯的妈妈聊过了
We talked to Felix's mom.
她说她看到两名拉丁裔  20多岁
She says she saw two Latinos, 20,
跳进一辆黑色的车  不过只有这些信息
jump into a dark car, but that's all we got.
肯定有人看到过他们
Somebody had to see them.
他们不可能就这么消失的
They didn't just disappear into thin air.
那好  咱们开始复核交通监控
All right, so let's double down on the traffic cams,
筛查更多目击证人出来吧
start canvassing for more witnesses.
要我说我们应该把这事当成内鬼作祟
Ask me, we should assume this is an inside job.
你在电话本上可查不到
You don't get the address of a stash house
藏毒藏匿点
in the yellow pages.
他说得对
He's right.
这些人肯定不是运气好
I mean, these guys aren't just getting lucky.
他们知道去哪找  什么时候去
They know where to go and when to go.
确实有可能是拉丁帮内部的人干的
You know, it could be someone inside the Latin Hoods.
我去联系帮派内部的熟人
I'ma reach out to a buddy in Gangs.
很好  追查下去
Good. Chase that.
-好  -其他人
- All right. - Everybody else,
发动你们的线人
reach out to your CIs,
多出些赏钱
and put some money on the street.
我深挖了一下这个鲁本·吉尔布莱特
So I dug into this Ruben Gilbright.
他暂住在皮尔森社区的旅馆里
He's staying at a halfway house in Pilsen.
查到地址了
Got his address.
你在想什么
What are you thinking, mm?
这个大陪审团的审判对象是你
You're the subject of this grand jury.
一旦有人看到你查这个人
Somebody sees you nail this guy,
他们肯定会治你个妨碍证人罪
they're gonna hit you with a tampering with a witness charge
更别提别的一大堆罪名了
on top of everything else.
老埃  相信我  我来办
Al, believe me. I got this.
抓住栅栏  抓住了
Grab the fence! Grab it.
-腿分开  -好的
- Spread your legs. - All right.
-分开腿  -我分开了大哥
- Spread your legs! - Oh, they're spread, man.
你口袋里不会藏着什么
You got anything in your pockets
-拿来捅我的东西吧  -没有  我没有
- that's gonna stick me? - No, I'm clean.
我做什么了
What'd I do?
我看见你贩毒了
I saw you selling drugs.
不  我没有  没有
No, I do--I wasn't--
你卖的什么  可卡因
What're you selling, coke?
海洛因
Huh? Heroin?
不  不是那些东西
No, it ain't like that.
他只是我的朋友
He was just my friend.
-他叫鲁本  -闭嘴
- That's Ruben. - Shut up.
不准看我
Do not look at me.
-好  -这是什么
- Okay. - What's this, hm?
-是鲁本给我的钱  -不准看我
- Ruben gave me that cash. - Don't look at me.
-这是什么  -是他给我的钱
- What is this? - He gave me that cash.
是吗  他就这么白白送你钱
Oh, really? He just gave it to you?
不  不是白给我的  是他借我的
No, he didn't give it to me. He loaned it to me.
我破产了
I'm broke.
他只是帮我的忙
He's just helping me out.
这事就当没有发生过  你听明白了吗
This never happened. You understand?
-什么  -听没听明白
- Yeah? - Do you understand?
明白
Yeah.
这地方离他在林肯公园的住处
Damn, this place is a step down
也就两三步啊
from his spot in Lincoln Park.
丹萨以前可是住能俯瞰公园的园景房的
Denza used to have this sweet pad overlooking the zoo.
他不再是森林之王了
He ain't the king of the jungle no more.
-有事吗  -我们来找雷
- Help you? - Yo, we're looking for Ray.
拜托  克里斯托  你穿件衣服
For God's sake, Crystal, put some clothes on
再来应门
before you answer the door.
真是的
Damn.
你们怎么来了
What are you guys doing here?
让人看见了我就暴露了
People see you with me-could blow my cover.
雷  我打过你电话  你不接
Ray, I called you. You didn't pick up.
你就没想到我忙着吗
Never occur to you I might be busy?
-我有别的客户的  -雷  那伙人
- I got other clients, you know? - Ray, the rip crew.
他们又袭击了一处藏毒屋
They just hit another stash house.
一个小男孩被流弹打死了
A tender age boy was killed in the crossfire.
-他们打死了个小孩  -是
- They killed a little boy? - Yeah.
我的天
Damn.
孩子妈说她看见
And her mom said that she saw
两个西裔坐着辆黑车跑了
two Hispanics leaving out of a dark car.
是海洛因吗
Heroin?
是  包装上有眼镜蛇标志
Yeah, with a cobra insignia on it.
让你想起来什么了吗
Does that ring any bells with you?
没有  除了让我也想吸两口
Nah, but I could start doing some sniffing.
好吧  这伙人就是墨西哥贩毒集团
All right. We're talking about Mexican cartel here,
也就是说你们得付我高危补贴了
which means I'm gonna need some hazard pay.
什么  才怪
No. What?
不行不行不行
No, no, no, no, no.
你给我们情报才能拿钱
You get payment when you deliver information,
而且你还得快点
which needs to happen soon.
我说了  我得抽两口
Like I said, I'ma start doing some sniffing.
可我们需要你鼻子灵光点
Well, I'ma need you to have a more powerful nose, then.
真的  就跟那种缉毒犬似的
For real, dog, like one of them damn truffle pigs,
因为我和我哥们已经砸了五百块了
'cause me and my partner already $500 in the hole, homie.
你哥们知道我的情报绝对值回票价
Your partner knows I always deliver gold.
那跟我丁点关系没有
That don't got nothing to do with me, though.
这事已经扯扯得太久了
It's been too long of a day for this crap, man.
是啊
Yeah.
这公寓只是我的伪装的一部分  你们懂的吧
This apartment's just part of my cover, you know what I mean?
我一般不住这的
It's not how I usually roll.
是啊  这样就合理得多了
Yeah, sure. That makes sense.
雷
Ray.
把情报搞来
Get the information!
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
芝加哥警署
市退休福利办
厄普顿
Upton.
我跟我在帮派里的熟人谈过了
I just talked to my guy in Gangs.
今天被抢的藏毒屋
The stash house that got robbed today
属于十六街小子帮
belonged to the 16th Street Boys,
而不是拉丁帮
not the Latin Hoods.
看来不是内鬼作案了
So much for the inside job theory.
是啊  我们又回到原点了
Yeah, which puts us back to square one.
好  我的线人得到两个西裔帮派分子的情报
All right, my CI's got intel on two Hispanic bangers
说他们从47街和拉辛大道的房子里转移毒品
moving product out of a house on 47th and Racine.
-有眼镜蛇标  -申请搜查证
- Cobra label. - Get a warrant.
我们不需要搜查证  房子没人住
We don't need a warrant. House is vacant.
出动吧
Let's hit it.
走
Go.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
不许动  芝加哥警察
Stop right there! Chicago PD!
站住  站住  芝加哥警察
Hey, l--hey, hey! Chicago PD!
放开我  我什么都没做
Come on, let me go! I didn't do anything!
-我们什么都没做  -站住不许动
- We didn't do nothing! - You stay right there!
站在那里  不许动
You stay right there! Don't you move!
安东尼奥  你上吧
So, Antonio, you got me?
-我来  -拜托别开枪  别开枪
- I got you. - Come on, don't shoot. Don't shoot.
-跪下  -毒品在哪
- Get on your knees. - Where are the drugs?
-我们这没毒品  -毒品在哪
- We ain't got no drugs! - Where are the drugs?
我们没毒品  你们滚一边去
We ain't got no drugs. Get out of my face.
这不是毒品吗
These the drugs?
这是合法的
That's legal.
把他带走
Get him out of here.
走
Let's go.
海洛因肯定藏在哪里了  我们来翻个遍
The heroin is here somewhere. Let's tear this place apart.
杰  你们那边还好吗
Jay, you guys good back there?
我们这边很顺利
Yeah, we're good out here.
另一只手
Other hand.
我发现了
I got something.
典型的陷阱式
Typical go-to trap.
如丹萨所说
Like Denza says,
他送的是金子
he delivers gold.
好吧
All right.
我查了这两个嫌犯
I ran the two offenders,
-米格尔·索托和胡安·费尔南德兹  -好
- Miguel Soto and Juan Fernandez. - Yeah.
都有私藏毒品的前科
They both have priors for possession.
发现武器了吗
You recover any weapons?
不  没有枪  技术部还在现场
No, there was no guns. Techs are still on the scene.
他们在查血迹和毛发
They're looking for blood and hair.
-就目前而言没发现  -有火药残留吗
- So far, nothing. - Any gunshot residue?
没有  但已经过去一会了
Negative, but it's been a while,
所以不代表没有
so doesn't mean anything.
好消息是  我们发现的海洛因
The good news is, the heroin we found--
是符合的  有眼镜蛇徽章
it's a match. It's got the cobra insignia.
海莉  把那小男孩的妈妈带到这儿来
Hailey, get the little boy's mother down here.
看看她能否指认
See if she can make a positive ID.
杰  你和金去和索托聊聊
All right, Jay, you and Kim talk to Soto.
你们去审费尔南德兹
You two take a run at Fernandez.
兄弟  我需要你帮我暂时指挥  好吗
Bro, I need you to take point for a bit. Cool?
一切还好吗
Everything all right?
没事  我只是有些事要处理
Yeah, just got some stuff I need to handle.
告诉你  如果我们藏了那么多毒品
I'm telling you, man, if we were holding that much dope,
就不会呆在那种破地方
we wouldn't be laying up in that dump.
从法律上说那是你的房子  你的毒品
Yeah, the law says your house, your dope.
那不是我家  我们只是暂时呆在那里
It's not my house. We was just crashing there.
我要是杀了3个人
I'd be crashing there too
我也会呆在那儿
if I just killed three people,
包括一个小孩
including a little kid.
我们和那事无关
We ain't got nothing to do with that.
下午你们在哪儿
Where were you this afternoon?
在家和我的兄弟喝酒
I was having a beer with my carnal at the house.
是啊  在不是你房子的家里
Right, at the house that isn't yours,
而且你也不知道那里有毒品
with the drugs that you didn't know were there.
-没错  -没错
- That's right. - "That's right."
没错
"That's right."
有人可以证明吗
You got anybody who can verify that?
我们单独在一起
We're alone.
就我们两个  喝啤酒
Just me and him, drinking cervezas.
我知道你们想把那个男孩的死算在我和他头上
I know you're trying to hang this dead kid on me and my boy,
-但我们是清白的  -你逃了
- but we're clean. - You ran, G.
那通常是心虚的人干的
That's usually what guilty people do.
拜托  有人不敲门就闯入
Come on, man. Somebody comes to the door without knocking,
那通常不是友善的拜访
it usually ain't a friendly visit.
这是菲利克斯
This is Felix.
10岁
He's ten years old.
他住在藏匿屋走廊
He lived in an apartment down the hallway
对面的公寓
from the stash house.
头上中弹
He caught a stray bullet in the head.
当时他在睡觉
He was taking a nap.
有什么好笑的
What could possibly be funny?
没什么好笑的
Nothing. Nothing's funny, man.
没什么吗
Nothing? Nothing?
我想知道
I want to know.
你想知道什么好笑吗
You want to know what's funny?
是的  来说说
I do. Please.
好笑的是一个芝加哥警察
What's funny is a Chicago cop
假装关心一个墨西哥男孩
pretending to care about a Mexican boy.
喂
Hey, man!
放开我
Get off me, man!
-你不能这样  -是吗
- Hey, you can't do this! - No?
叫你们同事过来
Ah, get your boy! Get your boy, man!
你不能这样
You can't do this!
叫你们的人来
Get your man!
放开他吧
Hey, let him go.
你不能这样
Ah, you can't do this!
鲁塞  放开他吧
Ruz, let him go.
他会有报应的
He gonna get his.
我们会把这些给你留在这里
We're gonna leave these here for you,
这样你就可以一直笑了
so you can keep laughing.
怎么样了
So where are we at?
他们都一口咬定剧本
Both dudes are sticking to the script.
声称和抢劫谋杀
They got nothing to do with the rips,
-无关  -不在场证明呢
- the murders. - Alibi?
在废弃房屋里喝酒
Drinking beer in the abandoned house.
我刚和菲利克斯的妈妈莎拉·蒙特罗聊了
I just talked with Sarah Montero, Felix's mom.
我给她看了嫌犯照片
I showed her a photo array of our suspects.
-认出了吗  -没有
- Get a positive ID? - No.
没有面熟的
Nobody familiar.
所以要么是她没认出来
So either she didn't get a good look,
要么就不是这些人
or these aren't our guys.
我赌第二个选项
My money's on choice B.
第二个  为什么
Choice B? Why?
我刚查了他们说
So I just checked out the store
自己买啤酒的店铺
the guys said they got their beer from.
时间是上午9:33
Timestamped 9:33 a.m.
藏匿屋被袭击是上午9:36
Stash house was hit at 9:36 a.m.
交通不堵而且一路绿灯开回来
So it's a 20-minute drive if they hit every green light
都需要20分钟
and no traffic.
我们抓错人了
We got the wrong guys.
谁给你的情报
Who the hell gave you the intel?
你耍我啊  雷
Kind of game you playing here, Ray?
你说什么啊
Now what are you talking about, man?
你送的是金子  对吗
You deliver gold, right? Yeah?
你送的是蠢蛋的金子
You deliver fool's gold!
你让我去抓的两个人是无辜的
Those two guys you put me onto--they're innocent.
-你确定吗  -确定
- Are you sure about that? - Yeah, I'm sure about that.
-他们的不在场证明无懈可击  -抱歉
- They have airtight alibis! - Well, I'm sorry.
我只是传递情报
Look, I was just passing along info.
哪来的情报
Where'd you get the info from?
瘾君子告诉我的  他知道街坊的各种消息
From a junkie. He knows the neighborhood inside and out.
你给我的情报是从瘾君子那得来的吗
You gave me a tip from a junkie?
当然
Of course I did!
不然从哪儿来  心脏手术师吗
Where else would I get it, a heart surgeon?
海洛因怎么会在那屋子里
How'd the heroin get in the house?
可能是他们从真正的抢劫犯那里买的吧
Well, maybe they bought it from the real rip crew.
我怎么知道
Why the hell would I know?
别再给我不准确的情报
No more weak-ass info.
知道了吗
All right?
你这样让我很难做
You put me in a real bad spot with all this.
让我理理  我让你难做
Let me get this straight. I put you in a bad spot?
是吗
Yeah?
你这是在和我开玩笑吗
What is that, some kind of joke?
哥们  你别给我整这套
Dude, don't put that on me.
你只需要作证
All you had to do was testify.
你本可以罩着我的
You could've covered my back!
我没看到开枪
I didn't see the shooting.
你只需要
All you had to do
看到看到他掏枪
was saw that you saw him reach for his pistol.
我在一个街区以外
I was a block away.
我什么也看不到
I didn't see a damn thing.
我只听到枪声
All I heard was gunshots.
内务部会弄清楚的
IAD would've figured out.
否则会伤害到你
It would've hurt you.
-伤害我  -是
- Hurt me? - Yeah!
看着我  哥们
Well, look at me, homie.
我并没有飞黄腾达吧
I'm not exactly rolling in high cotton, am I here?
我是想帮你
I'm trying to help you out.
给你工作
Give you work.
你只是同情我
You're giving me pity.
好  那你知道吗
All right, you know what, then?
我们现在就可以终止这次计划
We can end this arrangement right now.
分道扬镳
Go our separate ways.
不  没事的
No, I'm good.
我只是...
I'm just...
对不起  好吗
I'm sorry, all right?
让我回去
Let me get back out there,
打听打听
let me shake up some bushes,
我会将功补过的
and I'll make this right.
是吗
Yeah?
这次不起诉
No charge this time.
好
All right.
老大
Boss.
是我
Uh, yeah, it's me.
我想和你道歉
Uh, listen. I want to apologize to you.
怎么了
All right, what happened?
我的线人从他信任的人那里
My CI-- he got bad info
得到的是假消息
from somebody he trusted,
但是他要弥补我
but he's going to make it up to me.
-我盯着他呢  -好
- I'm on him. - Copy.
我得挂了  等等打给你
I gotta go. I'll call you later.
我叫鲁本  我是个瘾君子
My name is Ruben. I'm an addict.
你好  鲁本
Hi, Ruben.
我还是个父亲
I'm, uh, also a father.
有一个九岁的女儿
Got a nine-year-old daughter.
我已经戒了14个月零6天了
I've been sober for 14 months and six days,
还有
and, uh,
在因为嗑药缺席了
after all those years of being absent,
这么多年后
being high,
我女儿和我妻子接受了我
my daughter and my wife have let me back into their lives.
我很感激他们又给了一次
I'm so blessed they've given me another chance
当丈夫和父亲的机会
to be the husband and father
我知道  在我内心深处  我是的
I know, deep down, I really am,
他们对我的信念
and their faith in me
让生命变得有意义
makes life worth living,
帮我与残忍无情的疾病作斗争
and helps me battle this cruel and unforgiving disease.
谢了
Thanks.
和反黑组聊过了  没有风声  没有线索
Just talked to the gang unit. No chatter, no leads.
取证室也没有新进展
Nothing from the crime lab, either.
肯定有什么联系
There's gotta be some link,
能把那三个藏匿点互相联系起来
something that connects these three rips to each other.
刚和高效毒品走私地区数据库的联邦探员聊过
I just talked to a fed at HIDTA.
我觉得我找到联系了
Think I have a connection.
马里诺的缉毒队把三个藏匿点的搜查证
Turns out Marino's narcotics squad had sealed search warrants
都封起来了
for each of the three stash houses,
恩格尔伍德
但不知怎的  在搜查令批下来之前
but somehow, the rip crew was able to hit the stash houses
抢劫团伙能袭击藏匿点
before the search warrants were executed.
你是说有人给抢劫团伙泄密
You're saying someone tipped the rip crews off?
我是说团伙知道
I'm saying the rip crew knew exactly
藏匿点在哪里
where the stash houses were
把货都拿走了
and that they were loaded with product.
因为搜查证
Because of the search warrants.
我们的缉毒队有黑警
We got a dirty cop in Narcotics.
是的
Yeah.
肯尼
Hey, Kenny.
谢谢你能这么早赶来
Thanks for coming in early.
没什么
No problem.
我想这不是普通的社交
I'm guessing this isn't a social visit.
我也希望是
Wish it was.
走  我们走走吧
Come on, let's take a walk.
告诉我发生了什么
Tell me, what the hell is going on?
我们觉得你队里
Well, we think someone in your squad
有人向抢劫团伙泄露搜查证的信息
is leaking warrant intel to the rip crew.
听着  汉克  你来和我说这种事
Listen, Hank, you come to me with something like that,
最好不是你认为  最好是你确定
you better not think that. You better know it.
我只知道
Well, here's one thing I know.
前几个月  你们队白申请搜查令的次数
Last few months, your shop has more negative warrants
比这个城市的任何队都多
than any other squad in the city.
那是因为我们执行了更多搜查令
That's because we did more warrants.
或者是因为抢劫团伙在你们去之前就赶到了
Or it's because the rip crew got there before you did.
我们还知道
Here's another thing we know.
我们调查的这三个
Look, the three rips we're putting on this crew,
有尸体的藏匿点
where bodies were dropped,
他们都碰巧
they happened
是由你们的人
while search warrants were being drawn up
申请的搜查令
by your guys on those very spots.
他们知道什么时候藏匿点
They knew exactly when the stash houses
里面会有货
would be fat with product,
没人看着他们
and there'd be no eyes on them.
我们都知道抢劫团伙可以
Come on, look, huh? We all know that there's lots
用很多方法得到消息  对吗
of way for the intel to get to the rippers, all right?
法院  助理检察官办公室
Somebody in the courts, the ASA's office--
听着  听我说  问题是
Listen, listen. The problem is,
每个经手搜查证的助理检察官都不是同一个人
there were different ASAs on each warrant,
经手法官也不同  三个案子经手的法官有两名
and the judge was different on two of the three cases.
唯一的共同点就是你的队伍
The only common denominator here is your squad.
情况就是这样
It is what it is.
那你们要怎么办
All right, so what's the play?
设个藏匿点
Set up a stash house.
你告诉你的人你有确切的消息
I mean, you tell your guys you got some good intel
但毒品不会放很长时间
but the drugs won't be there long,
所以你需要一个紧急搜查令
so you need an emergency warrant.
如果抢劫团伙露面了  我们把他们抓住
And if the rip crew shows, we take them down,
查清楚是谁在泄密
and figure out who's behind the leak.
好  准备好了告诉我
Right, let me know when everyone's cozy.
收到
Copy that.
今天早上你跟退休局的吉米·奥谢聊了聊
Talked to Jimmy O'Shea down in the pension station this morning.
有没有什么要告诉我的  老埃
Anything you want to tell me, Al?
没有  不是你想的那样
No, it's not what you think.
你已经打了报告  我看着
Well, you put your papers in. Seems...
挺显而易见的
pretty black and white to me.
我没想辞职
I'm not looking to pull the pin.
我只是看看内务部什么反应
I'm just seeing where Internal Affairs is.
算是煤矿里探路的金丝雀
Little canary-in-the-coal-mine kind of thing.
如果申请没反应
Application gets flagged,
那我们就知道他们真的立案了
then we know the case they're building is real.
老大  我们都准备好了
Boss, we're all set.
我也好了
Me, too.
安稳就位
In position, nice and cozy.
好的  你呢  杰
Right, what about you, Jay?
好了  我可以了
Yeah, I'm good to go.
收到
Copy that.
想找吉尔布莱特的黑料会...
Catching Gilbright dirty is gonna be--
会很难
it's gonna be tough.
他已经戒毒一年多了
I mean, he's been sober over a year.
也没有复吸的迹象
There's no sign he's using.
他有女儿  有工作
He's got a daughter, job.
所以呢  我们准备一点
So? We improvise.
这人想洗白  老埃
Guy's trying to go clean, Al.
我们再想别的办法
We'll find another way out of this.
肯定会解决的
We'll figure it out.
来了两个拉美人  20几岁  深色衣服
Got two male Hispanics, 20s, dark clothing.
他们好像戴着滑雪面罩
Look like they're wearing ski masks.
其中一个人的口袋里有东西
One of them's got something in his pocket.
这就是我们的目标
These are our guys.
我们等他们撞门
We wait for them to hit that door.
海莉  你给指示
Hailey, you say when.
还不行
Not yet.
坚持一下
Hang tough.
警察  放下你们的武器
Police! Drop your weapons!
-你没事吧  -没事
- You good? - Good!
大家都没事吧
Everybody okay?
都没事
All good.
里面那人死了  他不肯退下
Guy inside is down. He's not getting back up,
完全不肯
not ever.
这个还活着
This one's still alive.
G5021  有人被警察枪击
5021 George. Shots fired by the police.
派一辆救护车到第47西街3627号
Roll an ambo to 3627 West 47th Street.
这里有多名罪犯中枪
We got multiple offenders down.
收到  G5021
Copy that, 5021 George.
所以这个马尔多纳多  能活下来吗
Okay, so this Maldonado-- is he gonna live?
还不知道  警长
We don't know yet, sarge.
等他在医院做完手术
Soon as he's done with surgery at Med,
杰和厄普顿会跟我们说
Jay and Upton will let us know.
马尔多纳多的武器跟杀了那个小男孩
Maldonado's weapon is a match to the Beretta .380
菲利克斯的贝瑞塔38手枪一致
that killed the little boy, Felix,
所以基本可以肯定就是这些人干的
so we're pretty positive these are the guys doing the rips.
他们的住处呢  我们搜查过了吗
All right, what about their apartment? We search it?
我们发现了三万元现金和三公斤的海洛因
Here we found 30 grand in cash and three keys of heroin,
品牌和上次从藏匿屋里
and the brand matches the one
拿到的一样  眼镜蛇
taken from the last stash house, Cobra.
所以我们找到了凶手
Okay, so we got the rippers.
现在只需要搞清楚他们跟谁合作
We just got to figure out who they're working with.
这个我有线索
I got a lead on that, too.
让技术人员调查了一下
Did some digging with the OCD techs.
你确定吗
You sure about this?
我只看到了一堆文件
Look, all I see here is paper.
文件不会骗人
Well, that paper don't lie.
最近你们组的技术管理终端
There's a pattern of queries on your OCD admin terminal
生成的搜查令都是无效的
for warrants generated by your squad
这很有问题啊
that later turned up negative.
每次都是同一个人在登陆
And each and every login comes from the exact same person.
这  这  这又不能代表什么
This--this--this doesn't make any sense.
肯尼  她查看了
Kenny, she was logging into cases
不是他们组调查的案子
her team wasn't involved with.
这些都在这个文件夹里
It's all right here in the folder.
一定要给她公平的待遇
Just make sure you give her a fair shake.
我会的  向你保证
I will. You have my word.
不好意思  罗哈斯警探
Excuse me, Detective Rojas.
你能进来一下吗
Can you come in here a minute, please?
请进
Come on in.
谢谢
Thank you.
博伊特警长和道森警探
Sergeant Voight and Detective Dawson
想跟你聊一点事情
just want to go over a few things with you.
是的  要坐一下吗
Yeah, you want to have a seat?
不用了
No, I'm good.
几个小时前我们抓到了那个抢劫团伙
Well, we caught that rip crew a few hours ago.
其中一个杀了一个小男孩
One that killed a little boy.
我听说了  恭喜
I heard. Congratulations.
谢谢你  但是
Thank you, but, uh,
案子还没结
case isn't closed.
最后发现他们在跟别人合作
Turns out they're working with someone else.
是的  有人在给他们
Yeah, someone was feeding these guys
藏匿点的信息
intel on the stash houses.
你之前接触过这两个混蛋吗
You ever have any previous dealing with these two punks?
古提瑞兹
Gutierrez?
马尔多纳多
Maldonado?
没有  从来没有
No, never.
那你认识跟这两个人有接触的人吗
You know anyone who runs with these two?
等等  这是什么意思
Wait, what the hell is this?
就谈谈而已
It's just a conversation.
谈个鬼
Conversation, my ass.
你们的意思是我是黑警
You saying I'm a dirty cop.
你是吗
Are you?
我才不管你是谁
I don't care who you are,
什么级别
or what your rank is,
你再这么说  我跟你没完
you say that out loud again, I'm coming for you.
所以要么拷上我
So either slap on the bracelets,
不然我就出去了
or I'm walking the hell out of here.
我就知道
I didn't think so.
所有的线索都指向罗哈斯
Everything we have points to Rojas,
马里诺队里其他人都没有嫌疑
and no one else, in Marino's crew.
好的  我们得找到她跟古提瑞兹
A'ight, before we can move on her,
或马尔多纳多的确切联系
we got to find a firm connection
然后才能对她采取行动
with either Maldonado or Gutierrez.
我们深入调查了  老大
Well, we dug deep, boss.
计算机取证没有发现任何异常
Computer forensics saw nothing unusual.
她的电话和这些人的
No common numbers between her phone
一次性电话之间  没有共同联系人
and the burners that we pulled off those guys.
基本上她就是缉毒警的明日之星  警长
I mean, she's basically the rising star of narcotics, Sarge.
纪律报告非常完美
Her disciplinary report is perfect.
异常华丽
Highly decorated.
我没看到任何不正常银行存款
I don't see any irregular bank deposits
或者任何表明她的生活超出正常水平的东西
or anything that shows she's living above her means.
她是警察  知道怎么掩盖行踪
Well, she is one of us. She knows how to cover her tracks.
如果是那样
Okay, if that's the case,
那她为什么那么粗心
why would she be careless enough
用自己的代码
to log into the OCD admin terminal
登录管理终端
with her own code?
别想从马尔多纳多那里问出东西了
Forget about getting anything out of Maldonado.
法医那里有他杀的人的尸体
ME's got a toe tag with his name on it.
等等  我好像有发现
Hold on. I might have something.
是这样
All right.
从马尔多纳多公寓的固话
A frequent call made from the land line
频繁打出去的一个电话  是打给他的表哥
at Maldonado's apartment comes back to his cousin,
"大弗兰克"本尼特的
"Big Frank" Bennett.
他目前保释出狱  等待毒品分销罪名的审判
He's out on bail, awaiting trial on a distribution charge.
虽然不确定
Might be a long shot,
不过他可能在帮自己的表弟销货
but maybe he was unloading product for his cousin.
那他有可能在过程中认识罗哈斯
Means he could've met Rojas along the way.
追查看看
Let's chase it.
那边
Right there.
There.
停
Stop.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
-举起手来  -不要开枪
- Let me see your hands! - Don't shoot, don't shoot!
-不要开枪  -举起手来
- Don't shoot me! - Put your hands on your head.
-我什么都没做  -举起手来
- I didn't do nothing, man. - Put 'em on your head!
-快  -抱紧
- Come on. - Lock your fingers!
知道了  知道了
All right, all right!
拜托  我什么都没做
Come on, man. I didn't do nothing.
这些东西都不是我的
Come on, none of that stuff belongs to me.
现在是了
It does now.
天啊
Man.
还说犯罪没好处
And they say crime doesn't pay.
-你们拿走吧  -什么
- Just take it. - What?
我会说你们没来过
I'll make believe you guys weren't here.
你还是收回你这话吧
I'm gonna make believe you didn't say that.
我有一个问题
I got one question.
别误会
Don't get it wrong.
你表弟关于藏匿点的消息是谁给的
Who was feeding your cousin the stash houses?
我不知道
I don't know.
你给我听着
You listen to me.
一个十岁的小男孩因为你刚才冲的东西
A ten-year-old boy caught a bullet to the head
头部中弹死了
because of that crap you were flushing,
所以我的朋友
so you, my friend,
-你面临的是谋杀指控  -拜托
- are looking at a felony murder charge. - Come on.
最后帮你自己的机会
Last chance to help yourself.
我不会再问第二遍
I'm not gonna ask again.
我就只知道是个黑警
Look, all I know is that it's a dirty cop.
他们一般在一个叫尼莫的酒吧见面
They would meet at some bar named Nemo's.
监控是72小时一循环的
Footage is on a 72-hour loop,
但是两天前他们绝对来过
but those guys were definitely in here two nights ago.
那她呢
Okay, what about her?
跟他们在一起吗
Was she with them?
我不确定  这里人很多
I'm not sure. We were slammed.
等等  那是他们
Hold on. There they go.
在那里
Right there.
能快进吗
Can you fast-forward beyond this, please?
等等
Hold up.
停
Stop.
后面桌子那里放大
Zoom in on that back table.
丹赞
Denza.
问题很简单
It's a simple question.
你给雷·丹赞关于
Were you giving Ray Denza information
疑似毒品藏匿点信息了吗
about suspected drug locations?
雷跟这一切有什么关系
What does Ray have to do with this?
-天啊  -上一次抢劫前
- Oh, my... - He was hanging out in Nemo's
他跟马尔多纳多和古提瑞兹在尼莫酒吧一起出现
with Maldonado and Gutierrez the night before the last rip.
丹赞吗  你确定
Denza? You sure about that?
确定  我们从监控里看到的
Yeah. We got it on video.
我猜他把你出卖
Look, I'm guessing it's just a matter of time
只是时间问题
before he gives you up.
伙计们  我不知道你们在说什么
Guys, I don't know what you're talking about.
丹赞的号码在你的手机上
Denza's number's all over your phone!
老大说你在花钱买他的情报
Boss says you were paying him for information.
他是我的线人
I use him as a CI.
他破产了
He-he--he's broke,
所以我帮了他  仅此而已
so I helped him out, but that's it.
好吧  那你帮帮我们
Okay, so help us out.
让我们明白为什么有人用你的代号和密码
Help us understand why somebody logged into the OCD database
登陆了数据库终端
using your code, your password.
怎么可能
How's that happen?
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
他耍了我
He played me.
怎么耍了你
Played you how?
天啊
God.
我让他在我那里住过几晚
I let him crash at my place for a few days.
我还给他了一把家里的钥匙
I even gave him a key.
你是说他窃取了你的电脑密码
So you're saying he stole your computer password?
只有这样才能说得通
That's the only thing that makes sense,
因为我什么都没泄露过
'cause I didn't leak a damn thing.
以我女儿发誓
On my baby girl.
难怪他告诉我假情报
No wonder he gave me bad information.
就是他把海洛因放在那栋房子里的
He's the one who planted the heroin in the house.
我怎么就没看出来
How'd I not see that?
你也是想帮兄弟一把
Trying to help a brother out.
是啊  我跟个白痴一样
Yeah, like an idiot.
-他在哪里  -他走了
- Where is he? - He's gone!
他在哪里  雷
Where the hell is he? Ray!
我不知道  真的  他今早上来
I don't know, I swear! Okay, he came this morning.
一副吓坏了的样子
He was all freaked out.
他打包了东西  说再也不回来了
He packed a bag and said he's never coming back.
所以说你不知道他在哪里或者哪里能找到他
So you don't know where he is or how to find him?
我不知道  他就那样走了
No, I don't know. He just left.
你要知道  一旦贩毒集团知道
You understand, as soon as the cartel
谁是整件事的幕后黑手
finds out who's behind this,
你要是不帮我们找到你的男人
they're gonna hang your man under a bridge
他们会把他吊死在桥下的
unless you help us find him.
雷是个成年人了
Ray is a grown-ass man, okay?
他得为自己的决定负责
He's got to live with the decisions he's made.
你真是冷酷
That's cold as hell.
我说的都是事实
I'm just telling you how it is.
克里斯托  我知道你认为
You know, Crystal, I know you think
你可以让这茬过去
you can tie this off, move on,
再去找个男人
find another dude,
但我告诉你
but I'm here to tell you,
没那么简单
it's not that simple.
你是一直在帮一个毒贩和杀人犯
You see, you've been helping a drug dealer and a murderer.
这意味着你将面临
Which means that you stand down to face
重罪共犯的控告
felony conspiracy charges.
你明白吗
You understand that?
-那样啊  -你知道吗
- It's like that, huh? - You know what?
你以为我们在吓唬你吗
You think we're playing with you?
-我们没有  -跟我们走
- Because we not. - Come on with us.
走吧
Come on.
-走吧  -等等
- Let's go. - Wait.
他的祖父在唐人街的船厂有艘船
His grandfather has a boat in a boatyard in Chinatown.
冬天的时候他把船放在那里
He keeps it there in the winter.
雷有时候睡在那里
Ray sleeps there sometimes.
-你说的都是真的吗  -没错
- You telling the truth? - Yes.
收到  老大
Yeah, copy that, boss.
我们会耐心等着  好的
We'll sit tight. A'ight.
不要太放松了  他们还有十分钟就来了
Don't get too comfortable. They're ten minutes out.
收到
Copy that.
他在那里
Hey, there he goes.
我们不能让他上那辆车  伙计
We can't let him get in that car, dog.
右边上  右边上
Go right. Go right!
雷
Ray!
你懂该怎么做
You know the drill.
乖乖的  把你的手举到我看得到的地方
Nice and easy. Keep your hands where I can see them.
拜托  亚当  不是你想的那样
Come on, Adam. It's not even what you think.
转过身看其他地方
Just turn around and look the other way.
让我走吧  你不会再看到我了
Let me go. You never see me again,
我发誓  我们就扯平了
I swear. We'll call it even!
跪下
Get on your knees.
恶棍杀了恶棍  仅此而已
It was just bad guys killing bad guys.
那个孩子呢
Yeah? What about the kid?
他才十岁
He was ten years old!
那不是我的错  你我都知道
That's not my fault! You and I both know
子弹又没长眼睛
bullets don't got no names on them!
不  雷
No, Ray.
结束了
It's over.
跪下
Get on your knees.
Get on your knees!
好吧  你说得对
A'ight, you're right.
结束了
It is over.
别犯傻了
Yo, don't get stupid.
别走向我
Stop walking at me.
雷
Ray.
举起手来
Let me see your hands!
你能看到我的手
You can see my hands.
但你看不到的是我的枪
But what you can't see is my gun.
别这样
Don't do this.
-做什么  -雷  别跟我耍花招了
- Do what? Huh? - Ray, don't play with me.
要是我在吓唬你呢
What if I'm bluffing?
亚当
Huh, Adam?
-要是没有枪呢  -不 别这样
- What if there is no gun? - No, don't do this to me!
别逼我开枪杀你
Do not make me shoot you!
-别往前走了  -那一枪射得很漂亮  亚当
- Don't go out like this. - It was a good shoot, Adam.
很干脆  教科书一般
Clean, by the book.
我知道
I know.
我看到他伸手去拿枪了
I saw him reach.
我知道
I know.
-是啊  但没人帮我  -我知道
- Yeah, but nobody helped me! - I know!
没人在意
Nobody cared!
-你想知道结局是什么吗  -雷
- You want to know what the kicker is? - Ray...
-进监狱  -雷
- In jail... - Ray!
-我还是名警察  -雷
- I'm still a cop. - Ray!
这意味着我必死无疑
Which means I'm a dead man!
-我一天也坚持不下去  -雷  我会开枪的
- I won't last a day - Ray, I will shoot you!
是不是很讽刺啊
How's that for some ironic bullshit?
趴下
Stay down.
没有枪  没有枪  你个混蛋
No gun. No gun, you son of a bitch.
你为什么不开枪杀了我
Why didn't you just shoot me, man?
-为什么  -起来
- Why? - Get up.
起来
Get up!
你应该开枪杀了我
You should've just shot me, man.
You shoulda just shot me, man!
奥林斯基怎么了
Hey, what's up with Olinsky?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
一封密信出现在我桌上
A confidential letter came across my desk
写着局长亲启
for the commander's eyes only.
我是警察  自然很好奇
I'm a policeman. I'm naturally curious.
埃尔文的养老金被标记了
Alvin's pension got flagged.
你知道为什么吗
You know why?
汉克
Hank?
说吧  告诉我
Oh, come on. It's me.
听着  抱歉  特鲁迪  我不能说
Look, I'm sorry, Trudy. I can't. I can't.
好吧
Okay.
芝加哥警察  举起手来
Chicago PD! Let me see your hands!
举起来
Get 'em up!
举高点
Get 'em up high!
等等  发生什么事了
Wait, w-what's going on?
这是干什么
What is this?
我是来接我女儿的
I'm here to pick up my daughter!
我做了什么
What did I do?
你身上藏了什么
What you got on you?
什么都没有
Nothing!
看看我找到了什么
Look what I found.
怎么回事  鲁本
What's going on? Ruben.
-拦住她  -不要
- Get her. - No!
-不  那不是我的  -怎么回事
- No, that's not mine! - What's going on?
不 你你们放在那里的
No, you guys planted it there!
你们当中一个人放的
One of you planted it there!
-不能这样  -鲁本
- This is not happening! - Ruben?
那不是我的  凯茜
It's not mine! Kathy...
你承诺过
You promised.
-那不是我的  我发誓  -你怎么能这样
- It's not mine, I swear! - How could you?
女士  请后退
Ma'am, stay back, please.
弄错了
This is all a mistake!
凯茜  那不是我的
Kathy, that's not mine!
伙计  这里
Hey, man. Here.
有点突破
Caught a break.
看起来鲁本又开始吸毒了
Looks like Ruben started using again.
缉毒队收到匿名举报
Narcotics got an anonymous tip.
在他的车里发现了一克海洛因
Found half a gram of heroin in his car.
可怜的家伙
Poor guy.
-他尽力了  是吧  -没错
- Tried his best, right? - Yeah.
摆脱自己的恶魔很难
It's not easy to outrun your demons.